CREATIVE DIRECTOR

Executive Profile

With a background in Design, Marketing, Video, Digital, Print, User Interface, and Web Design I have over a decade of experience in the field in which I have demonstrated a consistent trackable record of financial growth and success. As a Creative Director, I am comfortable leading large teams of Art Directors and supporting personnel through the concept and development cycles of creative projects. Execution of projects takes into account brand management, marketing, accounting, upper management, vendor management, and specific Client needs. An Online Portfolio of my work is available at http://www.sjenner.com

Skill Highlights

Adobe Photoshop , Premiere Pro , Fireworks , Catalyst , After Effects , Audition, Encore , Dreamweaver , Muse, InDesign , Illustrator , Acrobat, Flash , Camtasia, SnagIt, Enfocus Pitstop Pro, PageFlex, DotNetNuke, Rainbow, Serena Collage, Countless Codecs/Encoders, Microsoft Office, 3ds max, C++ and exposure to SQL

Core Accomplishments

Sales, Marketing, and Creative: Â

Established Archway's Creative Summit program, which resulted in the signing of multi-million dollar Clients and an established offering in
the Archway service pipeline. By Client request, we offer this service as part of the Client contract in order to generate up-sell opportunities,
priceless value add management of the accounts, and significant stickiness with Client base

Operations Management: Â

- Managed 16 direct reports
- Managed relationships with outside Agencies and Freelancers
- Handled all functions related to Creative Services offering, including but not limited to: Graphics, Print Collateral, Video, Motion Graphics (After Effects), Web, UI, Variable Data Templating, 3D, and Multimedia.

Professional Experience

5 Star Nutrition October 2009 to Current Creative Director Fort Wayne, IN

- Responsible for the projects of leading Fortune 500 Clients across 10 separate Industries within Archway, including but not limited to Sony, Ford, GM, IBM, Starbucks, Carls Jr, JPMorganChase, Citi, Bank of America, Lowes, Nestle, Campbells, Heineken, National Geographic, Microsoft, Telus, AT&T, American Eagle, the UFC, and more.
- Established a pipeline of revenue worth over 6M dollars.
- On time delivery rate of over 99% Established a Creative Services department consisting of 14 members and 7 divisions, including Design,
 Prepress, Technical Document Services, Templating, Multimedia, VDP, Mail, and Staging Presenting to key clients, including Fortune 500,
 senior management and directors on various matters, including design initiatives, departmental organization and strategy, process, and
 essential product offerings Utilization of Entire Adobe Creative Suite including but not limited to: InDesign, Photoshop, Fireworks,
 Illustrator, Premiere Pro, After Effects, Muse, Dreamweaver, Acrobat and more.
- Headed core design team responsible for concept and finished client work product, and senior management and board presentations and
 initiatives Through the capabilities offered by the Creatives Services department, bolstered and aided in the level of Client retention and
 services offered Responsible for meeting strict project deadlines around Graphic Design and the framework through which it supports
 Marketing and Sales Departments as well as our Clients Creation of Dynamic Driven artwork through Pageflex and the proprotary
 company software of Promonet.
- Established a complete business process that allows Archway to track a job from initial engagement and through to fulfillment Developed the
 ticketing system which serves as the backbone for Archway's Norcross and Vegas service centers, which are the headquarters of our Print,
 Templating, Prepress, Design, and Application Support services Extensive support to both Clients and Pre-Press throughout work cycle.
- Extensive experience with hand-coding and designing templates through the use of PageFlex.
- judgment graFix.

October 2005 to September 2009 Creative Director Denver, CO

- Responsible for driving team vision and execution throughout complex application development and graphic projects Selected, managed, and executed agreement with all vendor relationships around printer and hardware to manage pricing, timing, and quality Responsible for developing relationships and new sales opportunities with existing and new Clients Worked in coordination with internal staff and outside attorneys, including Fortune 100 organizations to plan strategy and case critical next steps to maximize the chance of a favorable verdict.
- Utilized Adobe Photoshop, Flash and Premiere Pro to create trial exhibits and presentations for televised, multi-million dollar jury trials, within State and Federal Court Concept, design, and production of all internal and external print and digital media Support and design of corporate website Formatted and arranged documents and other media for interactive courtroom presentations and onto boards.

Kimco Realty June 2004 to August 2005 Graphic, Web and Multimedia Designer Roseville, CA

Presented extensively to and worked closely with senior Bank management Regularly utilized Adobe Flash and Adobe Photoshop to design

website banners, advertisements, logos, concepts, animations and buttons Filmed, and then using Adobe Premiere, AfterEffects, Audition and Encore, edited and produced DVDs publicizing live events, training seminars, promotional activities and other essential internal bank affairs Through the use of Microsoft's Media Server 2003, internallystreamed encoded footage that maintained image integrity, while taking into account the Bank's limited bandwidth capabilities Key member of team that spearheaded and managed development of FirstMerit Bank's homepage and intranet Designed online newsletter for the Network Services Division, including interactive graphical interfaces Base support for Serena Collage (leading web content management application) KeyCorp (Fortune 500 Company.

January 2001 to January 2002 Graphic Designer City, STATE

- Presented designs to and worked extensively with senior corporate management and Quality Assurance.
- Extensively employed Adobe Photoshop to develop website graphics and interfaces.
- Led team executing graphical work for prototype websites, exclusively designed for KeyCorp's most affluent customers (top three percent).
- Utilizing Adobe Dreamweaver, designed team jump pages utilized in organizing and condensing information essential for KeyCorp employees.

Education

Kent State University 5 2005 BS : Computer Science State Computer Science Skills

Adobe, Acrobat, After Effects, After Effects, Photoshop, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Premiere, advertisements, application development, banners, business process, C++, homepage, hardware, Concept, Client, Clients, delivery, designing, Dreamweaver, driving, senior management, Fireworks, Flash, Graphic Design, graphics, graphic, IBM, Illustrator, image, InDesign, logos, Marketing, max, Mail, Microsoft Office, Multimedia, Network, newsletter, next, organizing, Prepress, Pre-Press, Presenting, presentations, pricing, printer, coding, quality, Quality Assurance, Sales, seminars, SQL, strategy, vision, website, web content, websites Additional Information

 AWARDS Art Awards: Ohio Governor's Art Award, Graphical Artist Scholastic Award, Multiple Art and Social Competitions including Portfolio Honors Above and Beyond Award (Archway Marketing Services) Excellence (FirstMerit Bank)